let quiz = [
    {
        question: "Where is the correct place to insert a JavaScript?",
        option: [
            "The head section",
            "Both the head section and the body section are correct",
            "The body section",
            "None of the above",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "How many ways are there with which we can declare a variable in javascript?",
        option: [
            "Only one",
            "Infinity many",
            "Three",
            "None of the above",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the type of variable data declare below const data=[]?",
        option: [
            "Object",
            "String",
            "Array",
            "None of the above",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question:
            "Which of the following javascript functions allows you to get user input data?",
        option: [
            "prompt",
            "alert",
            "confirm",
            "None of the above",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question:
            "Which of the following represents loops in javascript?",
        option: [
            "for",
            "while",
            "forEach",
            "All of the above",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "What scripting language is jQuery written in ",
        option: [
            "C++",
            "VBScript",
            "C#",
            "javaScript"],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "jQuery method is used to perform an asynchronous HTTP request?",
        option: [
            "jQuery.ajaxSetup",
            "jQuery.ajaxAsync",
            "jQuery.ajax",
            "None of the above",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question:
            "What is negative infinity in Java script?",
        option: [
            "Any of below",
            "number in JavaScript, derived by dividing number by a negative number ",
            "number in JavaScript, derived by dividing number by zero",
            "number in JavaScript, derived by dividing negative number by zero"],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Which function is a synonym for on()", 
        option: [
            "add()",
            "once()",
            "listeners()",
            "addListener()"],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is used for parsing JSON text?",
        option: [
            "jQuery.each()",
            "jQuery.NOcONFLICT()",
            "jQuery.parseJSON()",
            "None of the above"],
        answer: 3,
    },
];
